https://fisher.osu.edu/privacy-policy

Overview
Fisher College of Business at The Ohio State University recognizes the importance of privacy to visitors of our website. This privacy policy explains what type of information is collected from you when you visit any of the pages within the Fisher website.
Visitors under the age of 18 must obtain permission from their parents or guardians before sending any personal identifying information to any page within the Fisher College of Business website.
Fisher College of Business is committed to ensuring the privacy and accuracy of your confidential information. We do not actively share personal information gathered from our Web servers. However, because Fisher College of Business is a public institution, some information collected from the website, including information from our server logs, e-mail delivered to our website, and information collected from Web-based forms, may be subject to the Ohio Public Records Act. This means that while we do not actively share information, in some cases we may be compelled by law to release information gathered from our Web servers.
Fisher College of Business also complies with The Ohio State University's policy concerning privacy and release of student education records.
What Information is Collected?
All Fisher College of Business Web pages use the Google Analytics service to track IP address information. This assists the college in improving functionality and content, and in monitoring the website's performance. Data is used to provide answers to specific questions about the usage and performance of the website or individual Web pages; however, no personally identifying information is collected during the process. Except as defined above, no IP address data is shared with parties external to the university. Google Analytics may also track non-identifying demographic data that it has access to, including age, gender, and affinity/interest categories.
Some pages within the Fisher College of Business website require personal information in order to provide online services. Personal information is gathered and stored in a secure manner to prevent monitoring or interception. Fisher College of Business and its designated online service providers do not share personal information with third parties except as defined above.
Like all other Web servers, Fisher College of Business Web servers automatically create log files for each visitor who accesses our website. These "access logs" allow us to make our website more useful to visitors. The access logs do not record a visitor's name, address, phone number, credit card numbers, or any other personal identifying information. Rather, they contain some or all of the following information:
The Internet Protocol Address (IP Address) of machines which accessed our website
The date of the visit
The time of the visit
The path taken through our website
The browser being used
A list of files downloaded or viewed
Any errors encountered
All of the information collected by Fisher College of Business is used for internal purposes only and is not distributed to any other charitable, cultural, nonprofit organizations, or parties outside The Ohio State University.
Updates and Contact Information
Fisher College of Business, along with The Ohio State University, reserves the right to change this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted to this page as soon as reasonably possible, so please check this page periodically. Use of any Fisher College of Business Web pages constitutes consent to any policy then in effect.
Disclaimer of Liability
The information contained in this policy explains the Internet privacy policy and practices that Fisher College of Business at The Ohio State University has adopted for its official Web pages. In legal terms, it shall not be construed as a contractual promise, and the college reserves the right to amend it at any time without notice. Neither Fisher College of Business nor any of its units, programs, employees, agents, or individual trustees shall be held liable for any improper or incorrect use of the information described and/or contained in the college website and assumes no responsibility for anyone's use of the information.
How to Contact Us
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this website, or your dealings with this website, please contact us via e-mail at webmaster@fisher.osu.edu.
©2020 Fisher College of Business
2100 Neil Avenue, Columbus, Ohio 43210
If you have a disability and experience difficulty accessing this site,
please contact us for assistance via email at
fcob-accessibility@osu.edu.
